<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Uhnnews on CUPE Hospitals</title>
    <link>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/tags/uhnnews/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Uhnnews on CUPE Hospitals</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;2016 Canadian Union of Public Employees</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 09:00:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/tags/uhnnews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>OCHU/CUPE launch anti-violence at work campaign: Epidemic of Violence</title>
      <link>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/news/violence-campaign-2017-09-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/news/violence-campaign-2017-09-12/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Ontario hospitals don&amp;rsquo;t want you to know that violence against hospital staff is real and rampant,&amp;rdquo; says union taking public awareness campaign to radio today
 Media Release
October 17, 2017
TORONTO, ON - A small investment in a Plexiglass barrier would have prevented a patient from stabbing a Perth/Smiths Falls hospital admitting clerk in the neck. Better alarms would have enabled nurses at Hamilton&amp;rsquo;s St. Joseph&amp;rsquo;s Health Centre to summon help when a patient, asked to take his medication, became violent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To all non-union employees of UHN</title>
      <link>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/news/uhn-letter-2017-08-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 19:59:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/news/uhn-letter-2017-08-29/</guid>
      <description>Recently you received a letter from UHN in response to CUPE’s organizing drive. The letter you received contained some inaccuracies and outdated information. In this letter, you will find updated and accurate information regarding CUPE and unions in general.
The first issue that needs to be addressed is regarding the Ontario Liberal Government’s net zero bargaining policy. The government officially ended their net zero policy in the fall of 2016 after it began to fall apart thanks to union contract settlements.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>