<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Uhns on CUPE Hospitals</title>
    <link>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/uhn/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Uhns on CUPE Hospitals</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;2016 Canadian Union of Public Employees</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:53:42 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/uhn/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How does my workplace become unionized with CUPE?</title>
      <link>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/uhn/whycupe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 19:53:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/uhn/whycupe/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A percentage of not less than 40% of the employees must sign union membership cards, then an application for certification is submitted to the Ontario Labour Relations Board.  One week later the Ontario Labour Relations Board holds a secret ballot vote at your workplace.  In order for the union to be successful fifty percent plus one of the employees who cast a ballot must vote in favour of the union.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Locals &amp; Bargaining units: What is the difference?</title>
      <link>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/uhn/local-bargaining-unit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 19:53:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/uhn/local-bargaining-unit/</guid>
      <description>When you are thinking about joining a union there are can be confusion around what the process is and understanding union structure. Included in this is the difference between a ‘bargaining unit’ and a ‘local’.
Bargaining Unit If a new group of employees decides to join a union they are ‘certified’ under the Ontario Labour Relations Act (OLRA) as a ‘bargaining unit’ of unionized employees. Under the OLRA a Collective Agreement must be negotiated for each new certified bargaining unit of employees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clerical News - July</title>
      <link>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/uhn/uhn-clerical-july/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 16:43:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/uhn/uhn-clerical-july/</guid>
      <description>Technological changes pose particular issues for clerical staff  Digitization of medical records Automation of dicta-typing and medical transcription Electronic patient registration kiosks  These are just some examples of the revolution through technological change taking place in hospitals across Ontario, which is eliminating the jobs of clerical employees.
In our central bargaining with Ontario hospitals, CUPE is seeking increased protections against the impact of technological changes on clerical staff.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>