<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kingstonnews on CUPE Hospitals</title>
    <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/tags/kingstonnews/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kingstonnews on CUPE Hospitals</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;2016 Canadian Union of Public Employees</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 10:00:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://cupehospitals.ca/tags/kingstonnews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>150 Kingston hospital staff push for better hospital funding at large Ottawa rally Friday</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/kingston-funding-2017-10-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/kingston-funding-2017-10-27/</guid>
      <description>Click here to read the Kingston Whig-Standard article on the rally by Ian MacAlpine.
CUPE PRESS RELEASE KINGSTON, ON – More than 150 hospital staff from Kingston Health Sciences Centre KHSC), represented by the Canadian Union of Public Employees (CUPE 1974) will board several buses early Friday (October 27, 2017) morning and head to Ottawa. There, they will join hundreds of other hospital workers from across Ontario, for a noon rally at Ottawa’s Montfort Hospital, calling for better provincial funding for hospitals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RPN&#39;s have a strong voice with CUPE</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/rpn-info-2017-10-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/rpn-info-2017-10-20/</guid>
      <description>New infographic flyer explains why CUPE is the right union for RPNs.
Download the PDF version
Did you know that?
With nearly 80,000 members employed in hospitals, long-term care, community care and paramedicine, CUPE is Ontario’s largest health care union.
40,000 hospital staff working at more than 120 hospital sites in communities across Ontario, including Kingston, are CUPE members.
CUPE has the strongest job security protections and best collective agreement for RPNs in Ontario.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your right to join a union is protected by law in Ontario.</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/union-rights-2016-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/union-rights-2016-01-01/</guid>
      <description>The Ontario Labour Relations Act (OLRA) In Ontario the OLRA protects the rights of workers to join a Union. Sections 70 and 72 of the OLRA prohibit employers from interfering with an employee’s right to join a union and ensures that employees are free from coercion, intimidation, threats, promises or undue influence, including reprisals for their support and involvement with the union. If the employer violates those rights CUPE will file an Unfair Labour Practice application with the Labour Board.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>