<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Events on CUPE Hospitals</title>
    <link>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/events/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Events on CUPE Hospitals</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;2016 Canadian Union of Public Employees</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 08:59:22 +0630</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CUPE Eastern Ontario RPN Conference: Dec 1, 2017</title>
      <link>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/events/rpn-nov8/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 08:59:22 +0630</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/events/rpn-nov8/</guid>
      <description> CUPE local 1974, representing staff at Kingston Health Sciences, is pleased to sponsor an RPN conference for eastern Ontario RPNs.

Date: December 1 Time: 10 a.m.- 4 p.m. Location: City Hall, 216 Ontario Street, Kingston 
Agenda  Violence and hospital nursing Bargaining demands for registered practical nurses in 2017 Expanded scope of practice for RPNs recently announced by the College of Nurses  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Mike&#39;s Information Sessions October 10 &amp; 17, 2017</title>
      <link>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/events/stmikes-october10/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 16:00:00 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/events/stmikes-october10/</guid>
      <description>Coffee and light snacks will be served.
October 10: 10am-11pm  Join us at the Pantages Hotel  October 17: 10am-4pm  Join us at the Starbucks at 82 Adelaide Street East  Ask us your questions  what is a union and what do unions do? why did the employer send me a letter about unionization? what are my rights in the workplace? how can I get involved?  Lean more about the St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UHN Information Sessions October 11 &amp; 12, 2017</title>
      <link>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/events/uhn-october11-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 16:00:00 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/events/uhn-october11-12/</guid>
      <description>Coffee and light snacks will be served.
UHN Employees  October 11: 10am-4pm Jimmy’s Coffee at 84 Gerrard Street  UHN Western Hospital Employees  October 12: 10am-4pm Tim Hortons at 750 Dundas Street West  Ask us your questions  what is a union and what do unions do? why did the employer send me a letter about unionization? what are my rights in the workplace? how can I get involved?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>University Health Network Drop-ins August 30, Sept 6, 13</title>
      <link>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/events/uhn-dropin-aug-sept/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 16:00:00 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/events/uhn-dropin-aug-sept/</guid>
      <description>Coffee and light snacks will be served.
When:  August 30 September 6 September 13  Time:  10:00 am – 2:00 pm (drop in anytime)  Location: Jimmy’s Coffee (3 rd floor) - 84 Gerrard Street West (north side of Gerrard between Elizabeth and Bay)
Ask us… Do you have questions?
 what is a union and what do unions do? why did the employer send me a letter about unionization?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markham Stouffville Hospital Clerical Employees Information Meeting (Aug 15, 2017)</title>
      <link>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/events/msh-clerical-aug15/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 16:00:00 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/events/msh-clerical-aug15/</guid>
      <description>CUPE Information Meeting To All Markham Stouffville Hospital Clerical Employees
You are invited to attend an information session to find out more about CUPE’s Application under the Public Sector Labour Relation Transition Act (PSLRTA) to the Ontario Labour Relations Board and what that means for non union employees at MSH. Information as well on how to join CUPE and the protection CUPE can provide during this process will also be available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kingston General Merger Information Session August 2-3</title>
      <link>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/events/kingston-aug2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 08:59:22 +0630</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/events/kingston-aug2/</guid>
      <description>When: August 2 &amp;amp; 3
All day.
Location: CUPE 1974 office at Kingston General Hospital site
Ask us… There’s a lot going on at our new merged hospital (Kingston Health Sciences Centre).
Many of us have questions about this process, the protections in your CUPE 1974 collective agreement and the central bargaining now underway.
Drop by on August 2 and 3, tell us what’s on your mind.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>