<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stjoes on CUPE Hospitals</title>
    <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/tags/stjoes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stjoes on CUPE Hospitals</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;2016 Canadian Union of Public Employees</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 09:00:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://cupehospitals.ca/tags/stjoes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>OCHU/CUPE launch anti-violence at work campaign: Epidemic of Violence</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/violence-campaign-2017-09-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/violence-campaign-2017-09-12/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Ontario hospitals don&amp;rsquo;t want you to know that violence against hospital staff is real and rampant,&amp;rdquo; says union taking public awareness campaign to radio today
 Media Release
October 17, 2017
TORONTO, ON - A small investment in a Plexiglass barrier would have prevented a patient from stabbing a Perth/Smiths Falls hospital admitting clerk in the neck. Better alarms would have enabled nurses at Hamilton&amp;rsquo;s St. Joseph&amp;rsquo;s Health Centre to summon help when a patient, asked to take his medication, became violent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keep Hospitals Cooking</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/hosptial-cooking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2017 19:53:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/hosptial-cooking/</guid>
      <description>St. Joseph’s Health Centre is in the process of making a decision about how to prepare and deliver food in its cafeteria.
Rather than serve “TV dinner” style food from a factory operation outside of Toronto, we think the hospital should consider patient well-being and the needs of the community.
We are calling on St. Joseph’s to:  Serve food that is cooked in-house Use good quality, fresh ingredients Use locally sourced, organic food when possible Focus on patient well-being, not cutting corners  There is a local food solution Parkdale is already home to a local food movement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What if I am non-union?</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/mergers/articles/non-union/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/mergers/articles/non-union/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When hospitals merge, workers who are union members have a huge advantage over non-union workers. Union members are protected by a collective agreement that offers superior protection against layoffs. If your employer is considering a merger with other hospitals, you should seriously consider joining a union that will fight for your rights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harmonization: What is the process?</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/mergers/articles/harmonization/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/mergers/articles/harmonization/</guid>
      <description>What is Harmonization? Harmonization is the process of taking the Collective Agreements from all the union’s involved in the merger, along with any non union working conditions, and merging them into the new ‘first’ Collective Agreement.
Some employers see a merger as an opportunity to table concessions to Collective Agreements or non union working conditions but CUPE negotiates to maintain superior conditions and believes that you should not lose hard won rights and benefits due to a merger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Posting and Promotion Update for newly merged hospitals</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/mergers/articles/post-promotion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 20:59:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/mergers/articles/post-promotion/</guid>
      <description>As you know the employer recently put out a notice letting employees know that all employees can apply for jobs at all sites within the newly merger Hospital and this has raised a number of questions by our members. Over the last couple of weeks CUPE has met with the employer at both Providence and St. Joseph’s.
What should I do if I hold a position at more than one location?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>