<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Clerical on CUPE Hospitals</title>
    <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/tags/clerical/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Clerical on CUPE Hospitals</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;2016 Canadian Union of Public Employees</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 10:00:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://cupehospitals.ca/tags/clerical/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-union clerical are affected by the merger at St. Mike&#39;s: CUPE Podcast</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/merger-update1-2017-11-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/merger-update1-2017-11-05/</guid>
      <description>Podcast explaining the effect of the merger process at St. Mike&amp;rsquo;s on non-union clerical.
Listen to the podcast here.

Hello CUPE supporters!
As you may be aware, there has been a merger between Providence, St. Joseph’s and St. Michael’s hospitals as of August 1, 2017.
With any public sector merger such as this, there are government regulations that guide the process. When merging workplaces with many unions, there must be a vote by the workers to select a single union to represent the newly merged workplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clerical News - July</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/clerical/clerical-july/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 16:43:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/clerical/clerical-july/</guid>
      <description>Technological changes pose particular issues for clerical staff  Digitization of medical records Automation of dicta-typing and medical transcription Electronic patient registration kiosks  These are just some examples of the revolution through technological change taking place in hospitals across Ontario, which is eliminating the jobs of clerical employees.
In our central bargaining with Ontario hospitals, CUPE is seeking increased protections against the impact of technological changes on clerical staff.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>