<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stmikes on CUPE Hospitals</title>
    <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/categories/stmikes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stmikes on CUPE Hospitals</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;2016 Canadian Union of Public Employees</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 16:43:23 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://cupehospitals.ca/categories/stmikes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is it an advantage to be in a Union?</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/stmikes/advantage-stmikes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 16:43:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/stmikes/advantage-stmikes/</guid>
      <description>Hospital workers who are CUPE members have a huge advantage over non-union workers because CUPE members are protected by a strong Collective Agreement.
When you join a Union you negotiate a Collective Agreement that sets out such things as:
 Vacation Entitlement (unreduced percentage in lieu or time off, increased with length of service); Rates of Pay and regular procession through pay grids; Fair Shift Scheduling Process &amp;amp; schedules posted in advance; Job Security Language including due to technological change; Layoff &amp;amp; Recall Rights; Health &amp;amp; Safety; and Discipline &amp;amp; Termination for Just Cause only  When you have a Collective Agreement the employer must abide by the rights and benefits set out in the Contract and must follow any and all procedures set out there as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clerical News - July</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/msh/msh-clerical-july/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 16:43:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/msh/msh-clerical-july/</guid>
      <description>Technological changes pose particular issues for clerical staff  Digitization of medical records Automation of dicta-typing and medical transcription Electronic patient registration kiosks  These are just some examples of the revolution through technological change taking place in hospitals across Ontario, which is eliminating the jobs of clerical employees.
In our central bargaining with Ontario hospitals, CUPE is seeking increased protections against the impact of technological changes on clerical staff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clerical News - July</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/stmikes/clerical-july/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 16:43:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/stmikes/clerical-july/</guid>
      <description>Technological changes pose particular issues for clerical staff  Digitization of medical records Automation of dicta-typing and medical transcription Electronic patient registration kiosks  These are just some examples of the revolution through technological change taking place in hospitals across Ontario, which is eliminating the jobs of clerical employees.
In our central bargaining with Ontario hospitals, CUPE is seeking increased protections against the impact of technological changes on clerical staff.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>