<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mergers on CUPE Hospitals</title>
    <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/mergers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mergers on CUPE Hospitals</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;2016 Canadian Union of Public Employees</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 19:59:22 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://cupehospitals.ca/mergers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hospital Mergers Information</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/mergers/info/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 19:59:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/mergers/info/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hospitals are merging across Ontario. The result are run-off votes between unions in those hospitals where members choose which union will represent them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Providence, St. Joe&#39;s, St. Mike&#39;s Hospital Merger</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/mergers/sjsmp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 19:59:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/mergers/sjsmp/</guid>
      <description>CUPE Local 1590 has represented employees at Providence Healthcare since 1973. Since then the Local has expanded to include employees of DTZ who also work at Providence Healthcare as well as employees at Hazelton Retirement Residence. Currently the membership includes 700 fulltime, part time and casual workers.
The Local’s first priorities are to negotiate strong collective agreements and protect the rights of our members. As a CUPE Local that is part of CUPE’s Ontario Council of Hospital Unions (OCHU) we are part of CUPE’s Central Agreement and have the strongest job security and job promotion language of any health care union in Ontario.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kingston General Hospital and Hotel Dieu Hospital</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/mergers/kghd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 19:59:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/mergers/kghd/</guid>
      <description>On April 1, 2017, Kingston Health Sciences Centre (KHSC) began operating as a new &amp;ldquo;integrated&amp;rdquo; hospital.
Information Session on the Merger  Click here information on the info session August 2 &amp;amp; 3, 2017.  CUPE Newsletters  CUPE Local 1974 Newsletters Nursing News Clerical News PSW News  Additional Information  Why choose CUPE? CUPE&amp;rsquo;s detailed guide to PSLRTA I am not in a union, what should I do?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markham Stouffville Hospital</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/mergers/msh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 19:59:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/mergers/msh/</guid>
      <description>CUPE Local 3651 has represented the Full time service workers at Markham Stouffville Hospital since 1994. In 2015 we became the representative of the Part time Service workers at Markham Stouffville Hospital and negotiated their first Collective Agreement. CUPE Local 3651 now represents over 450 Full and Part time workers at Markham Stouffville Hospital.
As a member of OCHU, the Ontario Council of Hospital Unions, we bargain centrally, and locally, for the Collective Agreement that has the strongest job protection language in the province of Ontario.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rouge Valley Health System and the Lakeridge Health System</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/mergers/rvlh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 19:59:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/mergers/rvlh/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hospital workers have seen more than our share of change in the workplace. Hospital mergers similar to the one between the Rouge Valley Health System and the Lakeridge Health System are happening in several Ontario communities. While there will be many workplace and organizational transitions, the merger also brings changes at the local CUPE union and bargaining unit level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rouge Valley Health System and the Scarborough Hospital</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/mergers/rvsh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 19:59:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/mergers/rvsh/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hospital workers have seen more than our share of change in the workplace. Hospital mergers similar to the one between the Rouge Valley Health System and the Scarborough Hospital are happening in several Ontario communities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While there will be many workplace and organizational transitions, the merger also brings changes at the local CUPE union and bargaining unit level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For one, we have a new CUPE local union to reflect the reality of a new merged hospital.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What if I am non-union?</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/mergers/articles/non-union/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/mergers/articles/non-union/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When hospitals merge, workers who are union members have a huge advantage over non-union workers. Union members are protected by a collective agreement that offers superior protection against layoffs. If your employer is considering a merger with other hospitals, you should seriously consider joining a union that will fight for your rights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harmonization: What is the process?</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/mergers/articles/harmonization/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/mergers/articles/harmonization/</guid>
      <description>What is Harmonization? Harmonization is the process of taking the Collective Agreements from all the union’s involved in the merger, along with any non union working conditions, and merging them into the new ‘first’ Collective Agreement.
Some employers see a merger as an opportunity to table concessions to Collective Agreements or non union working conditions but CUPE negotiates to maintain superior conditions and believes that you should not lose hard won rights and benefits due to a merger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Posting and Promotion Update for newly merged hospitals</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/mergers/articles/post-promotion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 20:59:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/mergers/articles/post-promotion/</guid>
      <description>As you know the employer recently put out a notice letting employees know that all employees can apply for jobs at all sites within the newly merger Hospital and this has raised a number of questions by our members. Over the last couple of weeks CUPE has met with the employer at both Providence and St. Joseph’s.
What should I do if I hold a position at more than one location?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>