<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Canadian Union of Public Employees on CUPE Hospitals</title>
    <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/categories/canadian-union-of-public-employees/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Canadian Union of Public Employees on CUPE Hospitals</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;2016 Canadian Union of Public Employees</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 16:43:23 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://cupehospitals.ca/categories/canadian-union-of-public-employees/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Information about the merger</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/sjsmp/info/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 16:43:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/sjsmp/info/</guid>
      <description>Choosing a union to represent you in the workplace is extremely important. Choose CUPE.
At CUPE, we have dedicated staff and member-organizers to be there for you, through every step of the PSLRTA process. Together we are stronger.
CUPE is a great union with an excellent track record of protecting and making gains for our members.
 CUPE is Ontario’s largest union with over 75,000 CUPE members working in health care.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 19, 2017</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/nursing/june19/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2017 16:43:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/nursing/june19/</guid>
      <description>Nursing Graduate Guarantee Programme Changes Changes made to the Nursing Graduate Guarantee Programme in April concern CUPE because it more strongly encourages the hiring into full-time positions of nurses who have just graduated from community college.
Many RPNs work part-time for years waiting to acquire the seniority to post successfully into a full-time position with benefits.
Th real problem the Ministry of Health needs to address are the budget cuts to Ontario Hospitals.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>