<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on CUPE Hospitals</title>
    <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on CUPE Hospitals</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;2016 Canadian Union of Public Employees</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 02:58:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://cupehospitals.ca/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>This is a test</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/2017-11-22-this-is-a-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 02:58:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/2017-11-22-this-is-a-test/</guid>
      <description>This is a test Testing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CUPE Anti-Violence Campaign News</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/violence-news-2017-11-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 19:59:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/violence-news-2017-11-16/</guid>
      <description>CUPE/OCHU&amp;rsquo;s anti-violence campaign Epidemic of Violence received extensive media coverage. The media reported on the polling and stories of physical attacks, sexual harassment, verbal abuse, and violence in Ontario hospitals.
Every day, frontline caregivers are suffering serious injuries that lead to time off work and even post-traumatic stress disorder. Instead of protecting their staff, hospital managers discourage them from reporting incidents and have even fired a nurse for revealing the real epidemic of violence in healthcare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-union clerical are affected by the merger at St. Mike&#39;s: CUPE Podcast</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/merger-update1-2017-11-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/merger-update1-2017-11-05/</guid>
      <description>Podcast explaining the effect of the merger process at St. Mike&amp;rsquo;s on non-union clerical.
Listen to the podcast here.

Hello CUPE supporters!
As you may be aware, there has been a merger between Providence, St. Joseph’s and St. Michael’s hospitals as of August 1, 2017.
With any public sector merger such as this, there are government regulations that guide the process. When merging workplaces with many unions, there must be a vote by the workers to select a single union to represent the newly merged workplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>150 Kingston hospital staff push for better hospital funding at large Ottawa rally Friday</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/kingston-funding-2017-10-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/kingston-funding-2017-10-27/</guid>
      <description>Click here to read the Kingston Whig-Standard article on the rally by Ian MacAlpine.
CUPE PRESS RELEASE KINGSTON, ON – More than 150 hospital staff from Kingston Health Sciences Centre KHSC), represented by the Canadian Union of Public Employees (CUPE 1974) will board several buses early Friday (October 27, 2017) morning and head to Ottawa. There, they will join hundreds of other hospital workers from across Ontario, for a noon rally at Ottawa’s Montfort Hospital, calling for better provincial funding for hospitals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RPN&#39;s have a strong voice with CUPE</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/rpn-info-2017-10-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2017 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/rpn-info-2017-10-20/</guid>
      <description>New infographic flyer explains why CUPE is the right union for RPNs.
Download the PDF version
Did you know that?
With nearly 80,000 members employed in hospitals, long-term care, community care and paramedicine, CUPE is Ontario’s largest health care union.
40,000 hospital staff working at more than 120 hospital sites in communities across Ontario, including Kingston, are CUPE members.
CUPE has the strongest job security protections and best collective agreement for RPNs in Ontario.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OCHU/CUPE launch anti-violence at work campaign: Epidemic of Violence</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/violence-campaign-2017-09-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/violence-campaign-2017-09-12/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Ontario hospitals don&amp;rsquo;t want you to know that violence against hospital staff is real and rampant,&amp;rdquo; says union taking public awareness campaign to radio today
 Media Release
October 17, 2017
TORONTO, ON - A small investment in a Plexiglass barrier would have prevented a patient from stabbing a Perth/Smiths Falls hospital admitting clerk in the neck. Better alarms would have enabled nurses at Hamilton&amp;rsquo;s St. Joseph&amp;rsquo;s Health Centre to summon help when a patient, asked to take his medication, became violent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keep Hospitals Cooking</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/hosptial-cooking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2017 19:53:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/hosptial-cooking/</guid>
      <description>St. Joseph’s Health Centre is in the process of making a decision about how to prepare and deliver food in its cafeteria.
Rather than serve “TV dinner” style food from a factory operation outside of Toronto, we think the hospital should consider patient well-being and the needs of the community.
We are calling on St. Joseph’s to:  Serve food that is cooked in-house Use good quality, fresh ingredients Use locally sourced, organic food when possible Focus on patient well-being, not cutting corners  There is a local food solution Parkdale is already home to a local food movement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joining a Union</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/msh-joining-union/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 19:59:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/msh-joining-union/</guid>
      <description>Often during an union organizing drive workers and the employer will focus primarily on monetary issues.
Employers will often scare workers into believing that they will take home less as a result of paying union dues.
The fact is that unionized workers earn more than non union workers. That is one of the reasons why employers don&amp;rsquo;t want a union in the workplace. The other reason they don&amp;rsquo;t want a union is because they lose the absolute control they currently have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To all non-union employees of UHN</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/uhn-letter-2017-08-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 19:59:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/uhn-letter-2017-08-29/</guid>
      <description>Recently you received a letter from UHN in response to CUPE’s organizing drive. The letter you received contained some inaccuracies and outdated information. In this letter, you will find updated and accurate information regarding CUPE and unions in general.
The first issue that needs to be addressed is regarding the Ontario Liberal Government’s net zero bargaining policy. The government officially ended their net zero policy in the fall of 2016 after it began to fall apart thanks to union contract settlements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2017 hospital funding well below average, bad news for Kingston patient care, say care staff</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/kingston-2007-08-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 19:59:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/kingston-2007-08-02/</guid>
      <description>MEDIA RELEASE, August 2, 2017
KINGSTON, ON — Below average provincial funding of about 1.4 per cent for the newly amalgamated Kingston Health Sciences Centre (KHSC) in 2017, “is bad news for patient care and cause for alarm at a time of significant change,” said Canadian Union of Public Employees (CUPE) 1974 president Mike Rodrigues at a media conference today.
A general 3.1 per cent increase in hospital funding was proposed in the 2017 provincial budget last April.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What to expect from your Employer</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/managements-message-2016-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/managements-message-2016-01-01/</guid>
      <description>Management’s message A good employer will respect your right to make an informed decision about whether joining CUPE is the right choice for you and your colleagues. However, it&amp;rsquo;s not unusual for employers to be afraid that you will join the Union so they resort to using union busting companies or the tactics promoted by those companies. These tactics typically take one of two directions. Either they take the &amp;lsquo;sweet talking&amp;rsquo; direction or they choose to &amp;lsquo;exploit fear of the unknown&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your right to join a union is protected by law in Ontario.</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/union-rights-2016-01-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/news/union-rights-2016-01-01/</guid>
      <description>The Ontario Labour Relations Act (OLRA) In Ontario the OLRA protects the rights of workers to join a Union. Sections 70 and 72 of the OLRA prohibit employers from interfering with an employee’s right to join a union and ensures that employees are free from coercion, intimidation, threats, promises or undue influence, including reprisals for their support and involvement with the union. If the employer violates those rights CUPE will file an Unfair Labour Practice application with the Labour Board.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>