<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Providence on CUPE Hospitals</title>
    <link>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/tags/providence/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Providence on CUPE Hospitals</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;2016 Canadian Union of Public Employees</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/tags/providence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What if I am non-union?</title>
      <link>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/mergers/articles/non-union/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/mergers/articles/non-union/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When hospitals merge, workers who are union members have a huge advantage over non-union workers. Union members are protected by a collective agreement that offers superior protection against layoffs. If your employer is considering a merger with other hospitals, you should seriously consider joining a union that will fight for your rights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harmonization: What is the process?</title>
      <link>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/mergers/articles/harmonization/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/mergers/articles/harmonization/</guid>
      <description>What is Harmonization? Harmonization is the process of taking the Collective Agreements from all the union’s involved in the merger, along with any non union working conditions, and merging them into the new ‘first’ Collective Agreement.
Some employers see a merger as an opportunity to table concessions to Collective Agreements or non union working conditions but CUPE negotiates to maintain superior conditions and believes that you should not lose hard won rights and benefits due to a merger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Posting and Promotion Update for newly merged hospitals</title>
      <link>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/mergers/articles/post-promotion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 20:59:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/mergers/articles/post-promotion/</guid>
      <description>As you know the employer recently put out a notice letting employees know that all employees can apply for jobs at all sites within the newly merger Hospital and this has raised a number of questions by our members. Over the last couple of weeks CUPE has met with the employer at both Providence and St. Joseph’s.
What should I do if I hold a position at more than one location?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>