<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kingston on CUPE Hospitals</title>
    <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/tags/kingston/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kingston on CUPE Hospitals</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;2016 Canadian Union of Public Employees</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 08:59:22 +0630</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://cupehospitals.ca/tags/kingston/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CUPE Eastern Ontario RPN Conference: Dec 1, 2017</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/events/rpn-nov8/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 08:59:22 +0630</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/events/rpn-nov8/</guid>
      <description> CUPE local 1974, representing staff at Kingston Health Sciences, is pleased to sponsor an RPN conference for eastern Ontario RPNs.

Date: December 1 Time: 10 a.m.- 4 p.m. Location: City Hall, 216 Ontario Street, Kingston 
Agenda  Violence and hospital nursing Bargaining demands for registered practical nurses in 2017 Expanded scope of practice for RPNs recently announced by the College of Nurses  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kingston General Hospital and Hotel Dieu Hospital</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/mergers/kghd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 19:59:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/mergers/kghd/</guid>
      <description>On April 1, 2017, Kingston Health Sciences Centre (KHSC) began operating as a new &amp;ldquo;integrated&amp;rdquo; hospital.
Information Session on the Merger  Click here information on the info session August 2 &amp;amp; 3, 2017.  CUPE Newsletters  CUPE Local 1974 Newsletters Nursing News Clerical News PSW News  Additional Information  Why choose CUPE? CUPE&amp;rsquo;s detailed guide to PSLRTA I am not in a union, what should I do?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kingston General Merger Information Session August 2-3</title>
      <link>http://cupehospitals.ca/events/kingston-aug2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 08:59:22 +0630</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cupehospitals.ca/events/kingston-aug2/</guid>
      <description>When: August 2 &amp;amp; 3
All day.
Location: CUPE 1974 office at Kingston General Hospital site
Ask us… There’s a lot going on at our new merged hospital (Kingston Health Sciences Centre).
Many of us have questions about this process, the protections in your CUPE 1974 collective agreement and the central bargaining now underway.
Drop by on August 2 and 3, tell us what’s on your mind.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>