<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stmikesnews on CUPE Hospitals</title>
    <link>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/tags/stmikesnews/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stmikesnews on CUPE Hospitals</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;2016 Canadian Union of Public Employees</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 10:00:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/tags/stmikesnews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Non-union clerical are affected by the merger at St. Mike&#39;s: CUPE Podcast</title>
      <link>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/news/merger-update1-2017-11-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2017 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/news/merger-update1-2017-11-05/</guid>
      <description>Podcast explaining the effect of the merger process at St. Mike&amp;rsquo;s on non-union clerical.
Listen to the podcast here.

Hello CUPE supporters!
As you may be aware, there has been a merger between Providence, St. Joseph’s and St. Michael’s hospitals as of August 1, 2017.
With any public sector merger such as this, there are government regulations that guide the process. When merging workplaces with many unions, there must be a vote by the workers to select a single union to represent the newly merged workplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OCHU/CUPE launch anti-violence at work campaign: Epidemic of Violence</title>
      <link>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/news/violence-campaign-2017-09-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2017 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dreamy-bhabha-38106f.netlify.com/news/violence-campaign-2017-09-12/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Ontario hospitals don&amp;rsquo;t want you to know that violence against hospital staff is real and rampant,&amp;rdquo; says union taking public awareness campaign to radio today
 Media Release
October 17, 2017
TORONTO, ON - A small investment in a Plexiglass barrier would have prevented a patient from stabbing a Perth/Smiths Falls hospital admitting clerk in the neck. Better alarms would have enabled nurses at Hamilton&amp;rsquo;s St. Joseph&amp;rsquo;s Health Centre to summon help when a patient, asked to take his medication, became violent.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>